Rob Letts

Senior Front End Web Developer

Email: roblettsdev@gmail.com

Phone: +447449983319 Location: London, UK GitHub: rob-letts LinkedIn: robertletts Site: robletts.dev



HTML



SVG



CSS



SCSS



TailwindCSS



JavaScript



TypeScript



Vue.js



Vite



Nuxt



Cypress

Bio

Senior front end web developer based in South London specialising in modern CSS, interaction design, and design systems.

Advocate for universal accessibility and utilising platform standards to sustainably further positive web experiences.

Conscious and empathetic individual that prioritises open communication and empowering colleagues. Previous career in live events and music venue management.

Education

MSc, Computer Science - Distinction September 2020 - September 2021 Birkbeck, University of London

Employment

TixTrack - Senior Front End Engineer

October 2024 - Present

TixTrack - Front End Engineer

June 2022 - October 2024

Tech Stack: Vue.js | Vite | Cypress | .NET | Azure

International ticketing solutions for live events and museums - primarily for Broadway NYC and London's West End theatres.

- UI/UX and Design System specialist, bridging the gap between the Design and Front End teams
- Converting an existing Angular monolith into a new Vue architecture
- Complex SVG manipulation and state management for seat maps in admin dashboards and consumer purchasing context

Red Snapper - Junior Front End Web Developer

October 2021 - June 2022

Tech Stack: Vue.js | Laravel | TailwindCSS | GSAP

London-based web design and development agency offering web implementations and consultancy for a variety of clients, including the BBC and British Medical Journal.

- Implement dynamic UIs for Laravel back-ends
- Creating and maintaining landing pages for external clients